Burim Saliji

2 Towers Pl, Wongawilli 2530

Phone: 0413393532

Email: Saliji117@gmail.com

Professional Summary

I am A Motivated and skilled professional with over five years of experience in commercial and residential window installations, as well as service and warranty for a window and door manufacturer. Possesses exceptional skills in liaising with builders and customers to troubleshoot and resolve any issues with windows, doors, and hardware. Strong work ethic, effective time management, and problem-solving abilities combined with proficiency in hand and power tools and measuring equipment. Proven ability to work in a team environment and lead and manage small teams, with effective communication and conflict resolution skills. Also experienced in graphic arts, print production, and customer service. Currently enrolled in Coder Academy for Diploma in IT Web Development.

Focus Capabilities

- Manage Self: Aware of personal skills and strengths, willing to learn and undertake new challenges, resourceful in seeking relevant tools and knowledge, hardworking and able to work effectively both in a team and independently, open to feedback to improve skills and complete tasks to a high standard.
- Communicate Effectively: Use clear and concise communication to ensure
 understanding of job requirements, adjust communication style based on audience,
 communicate professionally with all stakeholders, value teamwork and input of others
 while also confidently making suggestions and developing action plans, consider
 different perspectives and contexts, respect diversity in communication, select
 appropriate communication method for the situation.
- Commit to Customer Service: Committed to customer service, able to communicate effectively with peers and customers, align personal goals with department values of Excellence, Equity, Accountability, Trust, Integrity, and Service, focus on identifying and providing what the customer requires to a high standard within required timeframe and budget, adaptable and flexible to cater to unexpected situations.
- Think and Solve Problems: Able to analyze and identify problems, use creativity and persistence to resolve issues, consider multiple angles and determine best possible solution, seek input from colleagues, willing to try new things and learn new skills, monitor and evaluate outcomes and determine best practices.

Technology: I am proficient in the use of the Microsoft Office suite, including Microsoft
Outlook for efficient communication and CAD software for project design.
Additionally, I have extensive experience utilizing Central for task management and
OneNote for record-keeping purposes. Furthermore, I possess fundamental skills in web
development and programming.

Qualifications

- Induction Safety Certificate
- Working at Heights Ticket
- Australian Driver License
- Cert III Graphic Arts
- High School Certificate

Skills

- Effective time management
- Problem-solving
- Fast learner
- Communication
- Ability to work in a team
- Ability to work under pressure

Employment History

Service and Warranty, Hanlon Windows, Wollongong | June 2021 – present

- Liaise with builders and customers to resolve any problems with windows, doors, and hardware
- Troubleshoot any issues with products and provide solutions
- Provide excellent customer service and support

Tradesman Window Installer, Sole Trader Under AL & B Saliji, Wollongong/Sydney | August 2014 – May 2021

- Install commercial and residential windows
- Fabricate windows
- Cut and fit glass
- Read and interpret site plans
- Level head and sill

- Caulk windows
- Install hardware
- Take site measurements
- Perform service works

Head Printer, Kwik Kopy Wollongong, Wollongong | May 2006-August 2014

- Ran and maintained 4-color press
- Worked on pre-press operations
- Cut and finished jobs
- Managed and ordered stock levels
- Liaised with customers
- Trained apprentices